http://www.courier.net.au/wp/about-us/privacy/

Readership
Your browser does not support iframes.
Last updated: June 24, 2020
This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the
collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the
Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects
You.
We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By
using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in
accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Interpretation and Definitions
Interpretation
The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions.
The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
Definitions
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:
You means the individual accessing or using the
Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such
individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.
Company (referred to as either “the Company”, “We”,
“Us” or “Our” in this Agreement) refers to F Teare Marston Pty Ltd, Mann
Street, Mount Barker, SA 5251.
Affiliate means an entity that controls, is
controlled by or is under common control with a party, where “control”
means ownership of 50% or more of the shares, equity interest or other
securities entitled to vote for election of directors or other managing
authority.
Account means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.
Website refers to The Courier News, accessible from https://www.courier.net.au
Service refers to the Website.
Country refers to: South Australia, Australia
Service Provider means any natural or legal person
who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to
third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to
facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company,
to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in
analyzing how the Service is used.
Third-party Social Media Service refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.
Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
Cookies are small files that are placed on Your
computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing the
details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.
Device means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.
Usage Data refers to data collected automatically,
either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service
infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
Collecting and Using Your Personal Data
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain
personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or
identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is
not limited to:
Usage Data
Usage Data
Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service.
Usage Data may include information such as Your Device’s Internet
Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the
pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit,
the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other
diagnostic data.
When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may
collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited
to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the
IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the
type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and
other diagnostic data.
We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You
visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile
device.
Tracking Technologies and Cookies
We use Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the
activity on Our Service and store certain information. Tracking
technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track
information and to improve and analyze Our Service.
You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate
when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You
may not be able to use some parts of our Service.
Cookies can be “Persistent” or “Session” Cookies. Persistent Cookies
remain on your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline,
while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close your web browser.
Learn more about cookies: All About Cookies.
We use both session and persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:
Necessary / Essential Cookies
Type: Session Cookies
Administered by: Us
Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services
available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its
features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of
user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked
for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You
with those services.
Cookies Policy / Notice Acceptance Cookies
Type: Persistent Cookies
Administered by: Us
Purpose: These Cookies identify if users have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.
Functionality Cookies
Type: Persistent Cookies
Administered by: Us
Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You
use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language
preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more
personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences
every time You use the Website.
For more information about the cookies we use and your choices
regarding cookies, please visit our Cookies Policy or the Cookies
section of our Privacy Policy.
Use of Your Personal Data
The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:
To provide and maintain our Service, including to monitor the usage of our Service.To manage Your Account: to manage Your registration
as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You
access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to
You as a registered user.For the performance of a contract: the development,
compliance and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products,
items or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us
through the Service.To contact You: To contact You by email, telephone
calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such
as a mobile application’s push notifications regarding updates or
informative communications related to the functionalities, products or
contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or
reasonable for their implementation.To provide You with news, special offers and
general information about other goods, services and events which we
offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or
enquired about unless You have opted not to receive such information.To manage Your requests: To attend and manage Your requests to Us.
We may share your personal information in the following situations:
With Service Providers: We may share Your personal information with Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, to contact You.For Business transfers: We may share or transfer
Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of,
any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or
a portion of our business to another company.With Affiliates: We may share Your information with
Our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor
this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include Our parent company and any
other subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that We
control or that are under common control with Us.With Business partners: We may share Your information with Our business partners to offer You certain products, services or promotions.With other users: when You share personal
information or otherwise interact in the public areas with other users,
such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly
distributed outside. If You interact with other users or register
through a Third-Party Social Media Service, Your contacts on the
Third-Party Social Media Service may see Your name, profile, pictures
and description of Your activity. Similarly, other users will be able to
view descriptions of Your activity, communicate with You and view Your
profile.
Retention of Your Personal Data
The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is
necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will
retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with
our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your
data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our
legal agreements and policies.
The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis
purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time,
except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve
the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain
this data for longer time periods.
Transfer of Your Personal Data
Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the
Company’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties
involved in the processing are located. It means that this information
may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of
Your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where
the data protection laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.
The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that
Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy
and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an
organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place
including the security of Your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of Your Personal Data
Business Transactions
If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale,
Your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before
Your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different
Privacy Policy.
Law enforcement
Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose
Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid
requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).
Other legal requirements
The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
Comply with a legal obligationProtect and defend the rights or property of the CompanyPrevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceProtect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the publicProtect against legal liability
Security of Your Personal Data
The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember
that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of
electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially
acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its
absolute security.
Links to Other Websites
Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated
by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that
third party’s site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy
of every site You visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content,
privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify
You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our
Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “Last
updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any
changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are
posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us:
By email: editor@courier.net.au
Subscribe to The Courier here, or order home delivery here.Read or download the digital edition here.
© 2020 F. Teare Marston Pty Ltd | Terms & Conditions | Admin: Log in| Site by Sema4 Media
